或许我不该把你一个人留在家里
Maybe l shouldn't
leave you alone
过周末
here for the weekend.
不，不
No, no, no.
没关系
Come on.
The kids￡-￡-
孩子们也得见见他们另一对爷爷奶奶
kids have to see
their other grandparents.
总不能让他们一直以为
We can't have them
growing up thinking
街对面的那对活宝是正常的，是不是？
what's across the street
is normal, right?
爸爸！爸爸！
Daddy! Daddy! Daddy!
Daddy! Daddy!
Daddy!
妈妈！妈妈！
Mommy! Mommy! Mommy!
Mommy! Mommy!
Mommy!
看吧？我说她会爱死这个娃娃的
See? l told you
she'd love that doll.
是啊，多谢你了，雷
Yeah, thanks
a lot, Ray.
去康乃迪克的一路上都会如此愉快
That's gonna be fun
all the way to Connecticut.
老兄，我真希望我能去
Man, l wish
l was going.
我能问几个问题吗？
Can l ask you guys
something?
你们上一次哭是什么时候？
When was the last time
you cried?
什么意思？为了比赛？
What do you mean?
About sports?
不，我是说真的哭
No, something real.
l mean really cried.
不是为了比赛？
So nothing with sports?
不是。比如上个星期，我在看
No. Like last week
l was watching
《亲爱的，我把孩子缩小了》
"Honey, l Shrunk
the Kids."
那个人拼命寻找被他缩小了的孩子
The guy was looking
for his shrunken kids
然后我就哭了
因为我觉得
and l cried
'cause l didn't think
我的爸爸不会像那样
去找我的
my father would come
looking for me.
要找到你并不难
lt wouldn't be hard
to find you.
没错，只要跟着
Yeah, you just look
under the cookie
在地板上移动的饼干就行了
that's moving
across the floor.
不，不
No, no, no.
不，伙计们。我能理解他说的感受
No, guys. l know what he's talking
about with the crying thing.
有一天，我送双胞胎去学前班
The other day, l dropped
my twins off at pre￡-school...
我看着他们走进去……
and l was watching
them go in, you know?
门就那么关上了
And just as the door
was closing,
我看见麦克拉着杰弗瑞的手……
l saw Michael take
Geoffrey's hand...
然后……
and...
我不知道
l don't know.
在你们嚎啕大哭前我最好还是先回家了
l'm going home before
you guys start making out.
是啊，我该走了
已经很晚了
Yeah, l gotta go.
lt's getting late. l gotta go.
－哇！等等，等等
－嘿，吉昂尼！
￡- Whoa! Wait, wait!
￡- Hey, Gianni.
上车后我告诉你我哭的故事
l'll tell you my cry
story in the car.
好极了！我肯定会吐的
Great! That'll be
my throw￡-up story.
哇！你们都在说什么呢？
Whoa! What are you
talking about?
我们才刚开始呢
We're just getting
started here.
－雷，我们在这里呆了4个钟头了
－还不到11点呢
￡- Ray, we've been here like four hours.
￡- lt's not even 1 1 :00.
我早上6点就起来了，累坏了
l've been up since 6:00 A.M.
l'm tired.
不会吧？这样就受不了了？嗯？
Come on.
What, you can't take it, huh?
你们这些没用的家伙！
还是不是男人啊？
You're wimps.
What, you're not men?
雷，刚才是你说你哭了
Ray, you're the one that
just told us you cry
就因为你的双胞胎是同性恋
because you think
your twins are gay.
故事的重点不是这个！
That wasn't the point
of the story!
我不想知道故事的重点
l don't want to know
the point of the story.
来吧，这是我难得的自由之夜
伙计们！道格！
Come on, it's my one night
of freedom here, guys! Doug!
噢，别这样！
Oh, come on!
我该走了，明天我还得早起呢
l probably should get going.
l have to get up early.
噢，已经很晚了吗？
Oh, is it getting late?
或许还不算晚
Maybe not.
搞什么鬼啊？
What the hell
is that?
现在已经12点半了！
也没那么晚啦
lt's 1 2:30.
Not that that's late.
－嘿
－嘿，怎么回事？你想干什么？
￡- Hey.
￡- Hey, what? What do you want?
孩子不在，黛博拉也不在
来吧，我们玩点什么？
No kids, no Debra.
Come on, what are we doing?
什么都不玩。
谢谢你过来看我
Nothing.
Thanks for stopping by.
来啊，来啊
伙计，今晚我是自由人
Come on!
Come on, man! l'm free here.
噢
Oh.
－嗨
－哈喽
￡- Hi.
￡- Hello.
我是艾琳
l'm Aileen.
我是雷，罗伯特的弟弟
l'm Ray.
Robert's brother.
呃，OK，我很抱歉
Yeah, uh,
okay, sorry.
你们两个请便
Look, you guys
get back to, uh,
继续你们刚才在沙发上做的事
whatever it was you
were doing on the couch.
还有，呃……
And, uh...
我们明天再谈
不是关于你们今晚做的事
we'll talk tomorrow.
Not about what you did.
马上走
Go now.
事实上，罗伯特
我最好还是回去了
Actually, Robert,
l'd better get going.
－不，不，留下
－是啊，留下
￡- No, no, stay.
￡- Yeah, stay.
－不了
－求你了，留下吧
￡- No.
￡- Please, please, stay.
太晚了，很高兴认识你，雷
lt's late.
Nice to meet you, Ray.
－我再打电话给你
－谁？我？噢，是他
￡- l'll call you.
￡- Who me? Oh him! Yeah, him.
是啊，打给他
一定要打给他
Yeah, call him.
Yeah, please call him.
噢～～！
Whoops.
－你见鬼地到这里来干什么？
－什么？
￡- What the hell is wrong with you?
￡- What?
我只想出来放松一下
l just wanted
to hang out.
我没想到误撞了“美女与野兽”
l didn't know l'd be walking in
on Beauty and the Beast.
我们什么时候有半夜出去放松的习惯了？
Since when do we
hang out at midnight?
怎么了？我现在还不想睡
What? l didn't want
to go to bed yet! Huh?
我何必一个人呆在空空的房子里
Come on, why should l
stay up in an empty house
我可以整晚做我想做的事
all night when l can
do whatever l want!
你简直不可理喻
You know,
you are unbelievable!
我准备不可理喻地放纵了
l'm unbelievably
ready to roll.
这就是我
哈哈嘿嘿
That's what l am.
Ha, ha, he, he!
－等一下，你说空房子？
－没错，我自由了
￡- Wait a minute, empty house?
￡- That's right, l'm free!
－黛博拉和孩子们不在家？
－没错
￡- Debra and the kids are away?
￡- Uh￡-huh.
嘿！嘿！吉酷滋～
吉酷滋！（按摩浴缸品牌）
Hey! Hey, Jacuzzi!
Jacuzzi!
& 吉酷滋，吉酷滋
吉吉吉吉酷滋！ &
& Jacuzzi, Jacuzzi,
Ja-ja-ja-jacuzzi &
& 泡沫涂满我的屁股 &
& Bubbles in my heinie &
& 泡沫涂满&
& Bubbles in &
& 我的屁股！ &
& My heinie￡-￡- &
怎么？
What?
你害怕一个人过夜
You're afraid to spend
the night alone.
你怎么从“泡沫涂满我的屁股”
里得出这个结论的？
How do you get that
from bubbles in my heinir?
雷，知你莫如我
Ray, it's me
you're talking to.
我们可是一起长大的
We use to share
a bedroom.
你害怕了
You get scared.
什么？你胡说八道
我才没有
What? You don't know what
you're talking about. l do not.
是吗？还记得一到晚上
Yeah? Remember how long
you had to keep
你就要把小夜灯开着不肯关
胆小鬼？
the Popeye nightlight,
scardey￡-pooh?
是啊，只要大力水手不来
Yeah, well, until Popeye
came along
你就不敢关走廊里的灯
you had to keep
the hallway light on.
只有爸爸讲了恐怖故事后才会这样
Only after one
of Dad's bedtime stories.
每天都如此
Which was every night.
听着，如果你晚上不敢睡觉
就打开电视机
Listen, if you're having trouble
sleeping just turn on the Tv.
我没有不敢睡觉
l'm not having
trouble sleeping.
我很好，OK？
我一点也不害怕，罗伯特
l'm fine, okay?
l'm not scared, Robert.
是啊
Yeah.
听你大哥的话
Listen to your
big brother.
OK？看看电视
Okay?
Watch some Tv.
探索频道，小家伙
Discovery Channel,
cubby.
大自然会让你平静下来的
Nature will put
you right out.
是啊是啊，除非是关于猴子的，是吧？
Yeah, yeah.
Unless it's about monkeys, right?
你那是什么意思？
What's that suppose
to mean?
没什么
Nothing.
l just, uh￡-￡-
我想起了那个鞋撑
l remember
a particular shoetree
放在你的壁橱里，有个影子……
in your closet
that had a shadow...
－够了！
－你总觉得是……
￡- All right!
￡- ...that you thought
一只举着斧头的猴子
looked like a monkey
holding an axe.
嘿，听着，我那时才10岁
Hey, listen,
l was 10 years old
而且我的鞋撑很大
and my shoetrees
were big.
－尖尖的嘴巴，还有斧子！
－好了，我现在已经不怕了
￡- Pointy holes and an axe.
￡- Yeah, l'm over it now!
是吗？你的壁橱里有没有鞋撑？
Oh, yeah?
Got any shoetrees in your closet?
这不关你的事
你该走了
lt's none of your business
and it's time for you to go.
行了，快滚吧
All right, get outta here!
－这里一点也不好玩
－没错，还有……
￡- This place is stupid.
￡- Yeah. Oh, and, uh,
祝你独自呆在那座又大又黑的房子里
好运
good luck in that big, dark house
you're gonna be all alone in.
也许并不是独自一人？
Or are you?
肯定有什么东西在
All right,
that was something.
谁在那儿？
Who is it there?
这样我就听不见凶手了
Now l can't hear
the murderer.
“母亲准备找一处阴凉的树荫”
The mother decides
to nurse its young
“来照顾她的孩子”
under the cooling shade
of a nearby tree.
“不幸的是，这个决定将使得小羚羊丧命”
Unfortunately, that decision
will cost the gazelle its life.
“一头狮子捉住了她的……”
The lion will catch her...
不，不！
No, no, no!!
多谢了，罗伯特
Thanks, Robert!
愚蠢的大自然
Stupid nature.
该死的娃娃！
Friggin' doll!
嘿
Hey.
噢，雷蒙德
你怎么起来了？
Oh, Raymond.
What are you doing up?
睡不着吗？亲爱的
Can't you sleep, dear?
不是，我想睡就可以睡
No, no.
No, l could sleep if l wanted to.
－我只是……
－啊！
￡- l just, uh￡-￡-
￡- Aw.
你想念黛博拉和孩子们
You miss Debra
and the kids.
－嗯
－是啊
￡- Aw.
￡- Yeah.
是啊，想他们
Yeah, them.
你怎么也没睡？
So, what are you doing
still awake?
我帮罗伯特煮点茶
l'm making tea
for Robert.
－罗伯特？
－是啊
￡- Robert?
￡- Yeah.
他们要把他的公寓消毒
They fumigated
his apartment today
他直到明天才能回家
and he can't go back home
until tomorrow.
－噢，真的吗？
－是的
￡- Oh, really?
￡- Yes.
他说那是军蚁
He said they had
army ants.
军蚁
Army ants.
你来这儿干什么？
Well, what are you
doing over here?
嘿，我只是顺道走过来看看
Hey, l just had to walk
across the street.
你可得开车来这儿，巴龙警官
You had to drive here,
Officer Barone.
－你们在说什么？
－雷害怕了
￡- What are you talking about?
￡- Ray's scared.
－嘿，你自己才害怕了
－什么意思？
￡- Hey, you're the one who's scared!
￡- What do you mean?
你病了？有麻烦了？
You sick?
You in trouble?
谁恐吓你了？
Someone bullying you?
－不是，妈妈
－那是什么？你怕什么？
￡- No, Ma.
￡- Then what? What are you scared of?
孤单
Being alone.
你指你的下半辈子？
You mean for the rest
of your life?
不，不过谢谢你提出这种可能性
No, but thanks for bringing up
that possibility.
－那是为什么？
－我不知道，妈
￡- Then what is it?
￡- l don't know, Ma.
你知道的，奇怪的声音
You know, noises.
狗，壁橱里的东西……
The dog.
Things in the closet. lt just￡-￡-
有时候会让我睡不着觉
雷蒙德也是这样的
sometimes it creeps me out,
you know? Raymond too!
嘿，嘿
说你自己就行了
Hey, hey, hey.
Speak for yourself here.
嘿，今晚是你先到我那里去的
Hey, you're the one who came
over to my place tonight.
是啊，哪有什么军蚁
Yes, and there were
no army ants.
噢，我的房子空荡荡的
Oh, my house is empty.
黛博拉走了
Debra's gone!
噢，不
我吓坏了
Oh, no!
l'm frightened.
闭嘴，超级蠢驴
Shut up,
ass of the world!
你闭嘴！顶级笨牛！
You shut up, schmuck
of the whole neighborhood!
－没我厉害！你这个白痴
－我知道没你厉害
￡- That's smaller, you idiot!
￡- l know it's smaller!
别吵了！ 别吵了！
Stop, stop, stop!
停下！
Stop!
雷蒙德，你哥哥可不是一只猴子
Raymond, your brother
is not a monkey.
有时候感到害怕是很自然的事情
There's nothing wrong
with being a little frightened.
－我们都有害怕的时候，不是吗？
－是啊
￡- We all get scared sometimes, right?
￡- Yeah.
你们可以……
And you can￡-￡-
there's no reason why you can't
你们可以随时随刻到这里来
没有关系
come over here every once
in a while. That's fine.
在你们感到害怕的时候，
有一个避风的港湾可以让你们依靠
Doesn't it make you feel good
that there's a place to go
感觉是不是很好？
罗比？
if you're feeling
scared, Robbie?
是啊，我想是的
Yeah, l guess.
雷蒙德？
Raymond?
哈喽，姑娘们
Hello, ladies.
－弗兰克！
－王八蛋！
￡- Frank!
￡- Jerk!
你干嘛要这样？他们已经吓坏了
Why do you do that?
They're scared already.
正因为如此我才吓他们
That's why
l did it.
你们都是成年人了，上帝啊
你们到底是怎么回事？
You're grown men, for God's sake.
What's wrong with you?
嘿，你才是罪魁祸首
Hey, you're the one who
started the whole thing.
这话是什么意思？
Well, what the hell's
that suppose to mean?
你不记得了吗？
我们壁橱里的奇怪雕像？
Oh, you don't remember the stories?
Gargoyles in our closet?
还有那个哥哥
总是想等我睡着了以后
Or a big brother who's just waiting
for me to fall asleep
来偷我的脑子？
so he can steal
my brain?
还有那个蜘蛛人弟弟？
Or a little brother
who's half￡-spider?
蜘蛛人
Half￡-spider.
是啊，有趣极了，爸爸
Yeah, very funny, Dad.
你们省省吧！
Give me a break!
你们自己要我讲的
You asked for them.
“吓吓我们吧，爸爸”
"Scare us, Daddy.
“给我们讲一个恐怖故事”
Tell us a scary story."
我们还要求开车来着
We also asked
to drive the car.
知道吗？你应该明白
You know?
l mean, you should know better.
你把我们吓坏了，我们都不敢睡觉
You scared the hell out of us.
We couldn't sleep.
是啊，很多次甚至还尿床了
Yeah, couple of times
we even wet our beds.
我可没尿过床
l never did that.
噢，弗兰克
Oh, Frank!
看看你对他们做了什么
Look what you did
to them!
别跟我来这套，玛丽
Don't give me that,
Marie!
你喜欢我吓他们
You loved it
when l scared them!
那样他们都会跑到你那儿
Then they'd come
running to you
你可以对他们又抱又亲又舔的
and you could hug and cuddle
and slobber all over them.
嘿，那感觉很不错
这可是我一个美好记忆
Hey, that was nice.
That's an actual good memory l have.
－她让我们平静下来
－是的
￡- She'd calm us down.
￡- Yeah.
她总是挠我的头
She use to scratch
my head.
那很管用
That helped.
我不想看见我的孩子们被吓着
l didn't like seeing
my boys scared.
－还记得黄油饼干吗？
－是啊，你还有吗？妈
￡- Remember butter cookies?
￡- Oh yeah, you got any of those, Ma?
当然了，亲爱的
我这就去拿
Oh, sure, honey.
Let me get them.
我要法式脆饼
l like the pretzel￡-
looking ones.
还记得我们一起上楼躲开他
Remember that we'd go upstairs
to our room to get away from him?
然后谈论麦滋队，一直到我们睡着
Then we'd talk about
the Mets till we feel asleep.
－是啊
－我很高兴有你在，小家伙
￡- Yeah.
￡- l'm glad you were there, cubby.
我也是，感觉很好
Yeah, me too.
lt was good.
－是的
－个人来说
￡- Yeah.
￡- Personally,
我喜欢妖精
l like leprechauns.
什么？
What?
妖精
Leprechauns.
可爱的爱尔兰小妖精
Cute harmless
little lrish guys.
不管我给你们讲什么恐怖故事
And whenever l'd tell
you guys a story,
我都会搭上一群小妖精来吓你们
l'd throw in a couple of leprechauns
to scare the bejesus outta you.
嘿，雷？
Hey, Ray?
我怎么会知道小雷蒙德害怕妖精的呢？
How did l know little Raymond
was afraid of leprechauns?
我不知道
l don't know.
你说呢？罗伯特
Any ideas, Robert?
哦，爸爸，别把矛头指向我
Oh, Dad, don't start
pointing fingers, okay?
－那不管用的，是不是，雷？
－没错
￡- That's not gonna work. Right, Ray?
￡- That's right.
他怎么会知道妖精的？
How did he know
about the leprechauns?
我不知道，不是我说的
说不定是妈妈
l don't know. lt wasn't me.
Maybe it was Ma.
我什么也不知道
l don't know
anything about that.
我只知道我给不了你们护身符
All l know is l couldn't serve you
Lucky Charms.
他是我的小间谍
He was me little spy.
－是你告诉他的！
－噢，好吧
￡- You told him!
￡- Oh, all right.
是我说的
Yes, l did.
l told him.
－罗伯特！
－你为什么要那么做？
￡- Robert!
￡- Why would you do that?
我想要听他讲恐怖故事
但又不想被吓着
l liked when he told us the stories
but l didn't want to get scared.
我不怕妖精
And l had no problem
with leprechauns.
噢，好啊！
你可以呼呼大睡
Oh, great!
So you could sleep and l could
而我却整晚不敢睡
等着那些小怪物
stay up all night waiting
for those little monsters
－来把我掳到他们的巢里去
－巢？
￡- to come and take me to their nest.
￡- Nest?
－没错，巢！
－我很抱歉，OK？
￡- That's right, nest!
￡- Listen, l'm sorry, okay?
我一直很自责
Don't think l didn't
hate myself for it.
别忘了，那段时间我总以为你是蜘蛛人
Don't forget. At that time l thought
you might be half￡-spider.
我给爸爸通风报信的那段时间
You know in those days when l was
running information to Dad,
我以为我尿床是因为太内疚了
l think the guilt was the cause
of my occasional bedwetting.
好吧，不管怎样，那都是过去的事了
All right, look, whatever.
lt was a long time ago.
是啊，但这是不对的
我们应该团结一致的，是不是？
Yeah, but it was wrong. We were
suppose to stick together, right?
－我是说，我们是亲兄弟
－兄弟才会这样吵吵闹闹的
￡- l mean, we're brothers.
￡- Brothers do those kind of things.
那不是好兄弟
Not good ones.
好吧，听着
有些事我得告诉你
All right, listen!
l gotta tell you something!
你从没尿过床
You never wet your bed.
我曾经……
l use to￡-￡-
等你睡着以后
l use to wait
until you fell asleep
把一杯水倒在你的床上
and then l'd pour a glass
of water in there with you.
－什么？
￡- What?!
我……
Well l￡-￡-
我不想自己看起来像个小孩
你知道吗？
l didn't want to always
look like a baby, you know?
一害怕就叫妈妈
Calling for Mom
when l was scared.
我知道如果你尿床了，她就会过来
l knew that she would come
if you wet your bed.
我总是弄不明白
为什么醒来就在你的身边
l always wondered why
l was up by your shoulders.
对不起，老兄
我只是……
l'm sorry, man.
l'm just￡-￡-
对不起！我那时才6岁
还很不懂事
Sorry! Look, l was six!
l was under a lot of pressure.
噢，你那么做，雷蒙德
Oh, you just did that,
Raymond,
只是希望和你妈妈亲近一点
'cause you wanted
to be near your mommy.
怎么样？当头一棒吧？
Well ain't this
a kick in the ass?
每个人都迫不及待地责备我
Everyone was so quick
to blame me for all of this,
但是看看你们自己吧
but look at you.
你们的手上都沾满了鲜血
You've all got blood
on your hands.
现在我要去睡觉了
Now l'm going back to bed
我要去继续睡觉了
and l'm gonna sleep
the sleep of the just.
好吧，我也回去了
All right, l'm going home.
l'm going home.
这场驱魔仪式把我累坏了
This little exorcism
wore me out.
罗伯特，来吧
你可以睡沙发
Robert, come on.
You can sleep on my couch.
晚安，姑娘们
Good night, girls!
－走吧
－晚安，小伙子们
￡- Come on, let's go.
￡- Good night, boys.
盖好辈子，别让臭虫咬了
Sleep tight.
Don't let the bedbugs bite.
臭虫没什么可怕的，你们很安全
Not that there are bedbugs.
You're perfectly safe.
－别忘了把门锁好
－知道了，妈
￡- But make sure you lock your door.
￡- Got it, Ma!
－因为邻居会……
－好了，我们知道了
￡- Because in the neighborhood￡-￡-
￡- Yeah, we know!
－嘿，来啊
－你想干什么？
￡- Hey, come on.
￡- What are you doing?
妈妈在沏茶
Mom's making
herself tea.
我们可以去吓爸爸
来啊，我们走
We can get Dad.
Come on, let's go.
他还在浴室，来啊，快来
He's still in the bathroom.
Come on, go, go.
－太棒了！
－是啊，进去进去
￡- This is so great!
￡- Yeah, get in, get in.
－报仇的机会来了
－没错
￡- Little payback time.
￡- Yeah.
－我们该怎么做？
－跳出去尖叫
￡- So how should we do it?
￡- We'll just jump out and scream.
好啊，就叫“我们来抓你了！！”
Yeah, like,
"We're gonna get you!"
或者“我们要吸血！”
或者“我要锤死你！”
Or, "We need blood!"
or "l got a hammer!"
不，不
No, no, no, just￡-￡-
－只要叫“啊～～～！”
－好啊，啊～～～～！
￡- just scream like, "Yeah!"
￡- Yeah, good. "Yeah!"
－噢～～～～！
－不要“噢～～！”
￡- Whooooo!
￡- No whooo!
－只要“啊～～～！”
－好的，啊～～！
￡- Just, "Yeah!"
￡- Yeah, "Yeah!"
－对，对
－这实在太有趣了
￡- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
￡- This is so fun, you know?
是啊
Yeah, yeah.
－我们得经常做
－是该多做几次
￡- We gotta do this more often.
￡- We should do this a lot.
或许我们吓得他越多
Maybe the more
we do it to him,
－我们自己就越不害怕
－是啊，以毒攻毒
￡- the less we'll be scared.
￡- Yeah, like therapy.
是啊，差不多
Yeah, something
like that.
下一次我们要在他淋浴时吓他
Next time we should
get him in the shower.
他来了！
There he is!
安静，安静
Shut up, shut up,
shut up!
－OK，我们什么时候出去？
－再等一会
￡- Okay, when do we go?
￡- No, we just wait.
－等他上床了再说
－好极了
￡- Wait until he gets into bed.
￡- Yeah, good.
舒舒服服地躺下吧，老家伙
Get comfortable there,
old man.
好好地
Nice￡-￡-
好好地放松
nice and relaxed.
来吧，玛丽，你怎么了？
Come on, Marie.
What's with that face?
－没关系
－噢，不，妈妈
￡- They're gonna be fine.
￡- Oh, no, Mom!
噢，我不想吓到她
Oh, l don't want
to scare her.
该死
Damn it!
－我们还是出去吧
－不，不
￡- Let's just walk out right now.
￡- No, no!
等一会，等他们睡着了
No, we'll wait.
We'll wait till they fall asleep.
我们再偷偷溜出去
Then we'll sneak out.
该死
Damn.
嘿，我们有段时间没做了吧？
Hey, you know what we
haven't done in a while?
什么？他们要做什么？
What? What haven't
they done?
过来
Come over here.
噢，不
Oh, no.
噢，不不不
Oh, no, no,
no, no, no, no!
千万不要！不要！
Please don't.
Don't, don't, don't,
别过去，妈
别过去
don't go over there, Ma.
Don't go, don't go.
－噢～～～
－我们在这儿！
￡- Oh, yeah!
￡- We're in here!
我们在这儿！我们什么都没看见
We're in here!
We didn't see anything!
我们在壁橱里！我们在壁橱里！
We were in the closet!
吓坏了吧？嗯？
Scared ya, huh?
你这个变态！
You're a sick man!
你发什么神经啊？
What the hell
is wrong with you?!
我来告诉你！
我来告诉你他发什么神经！
l'll tell you!
l'll tell you what's wrong with him!
－他是个变态！你是个变态！
－变态！
￡- He's a sick man! You're a sick man!
￡- Sick man!
你们想吓我，啊？
You tried to scare me,
huh?!
把公牛惹毛了，就尝尝牛角的厉害吧
When you mess with the bull,
you get the horns.
－这里怎么回事？
－又逮着他们了，玛丽
￡- What's going on here?
￡- Got 'em again, Marie!
－吓死他们了！
－噢，弗兰克
￡- Terrified them!
￡- Oh, Frank!
他是个变态，妈
He's a sick man, Ma!
我知道，他吓着你们了？
l know.
Did he scare you?
－嗯……
－噢，来吧
￡- Uh￡-huh.
￡- Oh, come on.
我们下楼去，好吗？
Let's go downstairs,
all right?
我给你们倒点可可
再吃一点黄油饼干
l'll make you boys some cocoa
and l still have the butter cookies.
没事了，亲爱的
Everything will be fine,
honey.
我会保护你们不被坏爸爸欺负的
l'll protect you
from your mean 'ol daddy.
这样不好吗？
我喜欢这感觉
lsn't this nice?
l love it!
差点把我自己也吓到了
Scared myself a little.
噢，真想念我的床
Oh, l missed
my bed.
－是啊
－让我看看
￡- Yeah.
￡- Let me see this.
什么？
What?
罗伯特戳到了我的肋骨
Robert's elbow
into my rib
在爸爸妈妈的壁橱里
in Mom and Dad's
closet.
说来话长
Long story.
恐怖故事
Scary.
翻译：lisa doll
yukii45@hotmail.com
谢谢观赏